Finding Aid for the Music Department Photograph Collection, circa 1920-2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Photographs, circa 1920-2008, I.
  - Julius Eastman, composer conducting Creative Associates in rehearsal, December 12 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-080)
  - Julius Eastman, composer conducting Creative Associates in rehearsal, December 12 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-081)
  - Julius Eastman, composer performing on piano with Yuji Takahashi, February 2 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-082)
  - Julius Eastman, composer performing on piano with Yuji Takahashi, February 2 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-083)
  - Julius Eastman, composer standing with Yuji Takahashi, February 2 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-084)
  - Julius Eastman, composer at piano, December 15 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-085)
  - Julius Eastman, composer singing at music stand, November 17 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-086)
  - Julius Eastman, composer in bed, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Gena, Peter (Box 2, Item MD02-087)
  - Julius Eastman, composer in bed, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Gena, Peter (Box 2, Item MD02-088)
  - Julius Eastman, composer performing (contact sheet), 1971-1972, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-089)
  - Julius Eastman, composer performing (contact sheet), 1971-1972, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-090)
  - Emerson String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Steiner, Christian (Box 3, Item MD03-001)
  - Donald Erb, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Century, Janet (Box 3, Item MD03-002)
  - David Felder, composer standing, 1990, 1 black and white photograph; Booth, Janice (Box 3, Item MD03-003)
  - David Felder, composer in studio at console, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-004)
  - David Felder, composer with violinist János Négyésy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-005)
  - Morton Feldman, composer, with image of Samuel Beckett superimposed, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Enser, Dennis and Mueckl, Dick (Box 3, Item MD03-006)
  - Morton Feldman, composer seated at piano with David Del Tredici standing, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-007)
  - Morton Feldman, composer standing with David Del Tredici seated at piano, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-008)
  - Morton Feldman, composer seated at piano with Jan Williams standing, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-009)
  - Morton Feldman, composer standing with David Del Tredici seated at piano, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-010)
  - Morton Feldman, composer with David Del Tredici (contact sheet), 1972, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-011)
  - Morton Feldman, composer with Creative Associates (contact sheet), 1972, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-012)
  - Morton Feldman, seated at piano surrounded by Creative Associates, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-013)
  - Morton Feldman, seated at piano surrounded by Creative Associates, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-014)
  - Morton Feldman, seated at piano surrounded by Creative Associates, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-015)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor sitting at table with composers, April 27 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Doran, William (Box 3, Item MD03-016)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor standing at piano with composers, April 27 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Doran, William (Box 3, Item MD03-017)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor at radio interview with WBFO, 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-018)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor at radio interview with WBFO, 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-019)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor at 3rd Webern Festival, October 28 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-020)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conducting Creative Associates, 1967-1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-021)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conferring with Renée Levine and Henri Pousseur, February 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-022)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conferring with Renée Levine and Henri Pousseur, February 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-023)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor, February 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-024)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-025)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-026)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-027)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-028)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-029)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-030)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor seated at piano at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-031)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor standing onstage at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-032)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor standing onstage at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-033)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor standing onstage at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-034)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor standing onstage at Second Festival of the Arts, March 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-035)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor with administrators and musicians, Spring 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-036)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor standing with Julius Eastman, April 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-037)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor with Lejaren Hiller, November 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-038)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor with Lejaren Hiller, November 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-039)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor onstage with Douglas Davis, 1970-1971, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item MD03-040)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conducting Creative Associates in rehearsal, Spring 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-041)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor rehearsing with Creative Associates, December 4 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 3, Item MD03-042)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor, performance of his M.A.P. (Musicians at Play) by Creative Associates, December 4 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 3, Item MD03-043)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor, performance of his M.A.P. (Musicians at Play) by Creative Associates, December 4 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 3, Item MD03-044)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor, performance of his M.A.P. (Musicians at Play) by Creative Associates, December 4 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 3, Item MD03-045)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor rehearsing with Creative Associates, December 4 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 3, Item MD03-046)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor rehearsing with Creative Associates, December 4 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 3, Item MD03-047)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conducting rehearsal with singers, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-048)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conducting rehearsal with singers, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-049)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor conducting rehearsal with singers, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 3, Item MD03-050)
  - Lukas Foss, composer/conductor rehearsing Stravinsky's L'histoire du soldat, October 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 3, Item MD03-051)
  - Stuart Granville Fox, guitarist rehearsing with Creative Associates, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-001)
  - Stuart Granville Fox, guitarist rehearsing with Creative Associates, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-002)
  - Stuart Granville Fox, guitarist playing clarinet, 1970-1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-003)
  - Paul Zonn (clarinet), Edward Yadzinski (bass clarinet), Robert Martin (violoncello, and Richard Dufallo (conductor), October 29 1966, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-004)
  - Sherman Friedland, clarinetist seated with instrument in lap, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-005)
  - Sherman Friedland, clarinetist seated with instrument in lap, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-006)
  - Sherman Friedland, clarinetist seated with instrument in lap, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-007)
  - Sherman Friedland, clarinetist seated with instrument in lap, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-008)
  - Paul Zonn, clarinetist with Robert Martin, violoncello and Ed Burnham, percussion, 1966-1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-009)
  - Ivar Frounberg, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-010)
  - David R. Fuller playing harpsichord, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Delaney, Ric (Box 4, Item MD04-011)
  - David R. Fuller playing harpsichord, November 22 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 4, Item MD04-012)
  - Livingston Gearhart, composer at piano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-013)
  - Livingston Gearhart, composer at piano in class, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-014)
  - Livingston Gearhart, composer at piano in class, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-015)
  - Livingston Gearhart, composer at piano in class, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-016)
  - David Gibson holding violoncello onstage with Creative Associates, May 4 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-017)
  - Philip Glass, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bentham, John (Box 4, Item MD04-018)
  - Vinko Globokar, composer, 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Croix, Patrick (Box 4, Item MD04-019)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist performing, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-020)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist performing with Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-021)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-022)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist performing with Creative Associates, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-023)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, Luciano Berio watching, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-024)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, Luciano Berio watching, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-025)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, Luciano Berio watching, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-026)
  - Anne Graff, vocalist rehearsing with Creative Associates, Luciano Berio watching, February 12 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-027)
  - Guarneri Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Haeften, Dorothea von (Box 4, Item MD04-028)
  - Jacques Guyonnet, composer, conducting Creative Associates, May 3 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-029)
  - Jacques Guyonnet, composer, conducting Creative Associates, May 3 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-030)
  - Jacques Guyonnet, composer, conducting Creative Associates, May 3 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-031)
  - Jacques Guyonnet, composer, conducting Creative Associates, May 3 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-032)
  - Thomas Halpin, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-033)
  - Barbara Harbach, organist/harpsichordist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-034)
  - Barbara Harbach, organist/harpsichordist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-035)
  - Lynn Harbold, percussionist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-036)
  - Jon Hassell, composer with installation piece, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-037)
  - Jon Hassell installation piece (Hassell not shown), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-038)
  - Jon Hassell, composer with installation piece, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-039)
  - Jon Hassell, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-040)
  - Jon Hassell, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-041)
  - Charles Haupt, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-042)
  - Charles Haupt, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-043)
  - Charles Haupt, violinist performing with Miriam Abramowitsch, November 5 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-044)
  - Charles Haupt, violinist playing (face in shadow), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-045)
  - Charles Haupt, violinist accompanied by William C. Kothe, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-046)
  - Harpsichord built by Eric Herz (1963 instrument), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-047)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer, standing near electronic equipment, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-048)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-049)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-050)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer, holding score, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-051)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Rage over the lost Beethoven, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 4, Item MD04-052)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-053)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-054)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-055)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-056)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-057)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-058)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-059)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-060)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-061)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-062)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-063)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-064)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-065)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Three rituals for two percussionists and lights, May 1 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 4, Item MD04-066)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Avalanche for pitchman, prima donna, player piano, percussionist, and pre-recorded playback), November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-067)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Avalanche for pitchman, prima donna, player piano, percussionist, and pre-recorded playback), November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-068)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Avalanche for pitchman, prima donna, player piano, percussionist, and pre-recorded playback), November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-069)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Avalanche for pitchman, prima donna, player piano, percussionist, and pre-recorded playback), November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-070)
  - Performance of Lejaren Hiller's Avalanche for pitchman, prima donna, player piano, percussionist, and pre-recorded playback), November 3 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 4, Item MD04-071)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer conducting Creative Associates (contact sheet), 1977-1978, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-072)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer meeting with Creative Associates (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Seman, David (Box 4, Item MD04-073)
  - Lejaren Arthur Hiller, composer meeting with Creative Associates (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-074)
  - Performance of HPSCHD, composition by John Cage and Lejaren Hiller, 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Drysdale, Donna (Box 4, Item MD04-075)
  - Performance of HPSCHD, composition by John Cage and Lejaren Hiller, May 16 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-076)
  - Performance of HPSCHD, composition by John Cage and Lejaren Hiller, May 16 1969, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item MD04-077)
  - Warren Hoffer conducting Creative Associates, 1966-1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tobin-Willig, Nancy (Box 5, Item MD05-001)
  - Jay Humeston, violoncellist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-002)
  - Jay Humeston, violoncellist with Buell Neidlinger and unidentified violinist performing, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-003)
  - Jay Humeston, violoncellist in shadow, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-004)
  - Jay Humeston, violoncellist, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-005)
  - Jay Humeston, violoncellist, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-006)
  - Jay Humeston, violoncellist, 1964-1965, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-007)
  - James Hurt, actor in stretch suit, May 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 5, Item MD05-008)
  - James Hurt, actor in stretch suit, May 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 5, Item MD05-009)
  - James Hurt, actor in stretch suit, May 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 5, Item MD05-010)
  - James Hurt, actor with Creative Associates, 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-011)
  - Charles Joseph, violinist in playing position, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-012)
  - Charles Joseph, violinist in rest position, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-013)
  - Charles Joseph, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-014)
  - Juilliard String Quartet, seated and playing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-015)
  - Juilliard String Quartet, against white background, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-016)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-017)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-018)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-019)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-020)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-021)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-022)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-023)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-024)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-025)
  - Mauricio Kagel, composer (his Sur scene), March 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 5, Item MD05-026)
  - Dennis Kahle, percussionist, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 5, Item MD05-027)
  - Leon Kirchner, composer seated in chair, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item MD05-028)